Jasper Drescher

Breda, The Netherlands • (+31) 6 50128363 • jasperdre@gmail.com • jasperdre.com

Summary

Programming student with a passion for game development. Involved in the development of gameplay, tools and engines for multiple games and platforms. Experience with project management and pipelines. Contributor to open-source projects and attendee of game events.

Skills

Programming languages: C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, CMake

Software applications: Visual Studio, Unity, Unreal Engine, 3DS Max, Blender

Experience

Junior Software Developer

CortexArts

Arnhem, The Netherlands September 2014 – present

- Develop tools using Unity Editor, Java and C#
- Develop physics-based gameplay mechanics using Unity Engine and C#
- Develop dynamic websites using PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Participate in Dutch Game Garden Incubation workshops
- Created 3D art assets using 3DS Max, Blender and Adobe Photoshop

Waiter Vlissingen, The Netherlands DOK 14 July 2018 – September 2018

Retail Clerk Arnhem, The Netherlands Jumbo Supermarkten *December 2014 – March 2015*

Education

Bachelor of Science in Creative Media and Game TechnologiesBreda University of Applied Sciences
GPA 3.5/4.0

Breda, The Netherlands September 2016 – expected 2020

Awards

Best Programming Year 2

IGAD Game Awards, Breda University of Applied Sciences June 2018

• Winner Best Programming for Drivinity.